(Leonard:)Hang on.
They're showing a digital Time Bandits.
You wouldn't wanna come, would you?
(Penny:)Not really, no.
(Sheldon:)All right. Invitation pointlessly offered,
declined as expected.
(Sheldon:)Everyone's civil, nobody's fighting.
Have a nice evening.
Just give us a minute?
(Howard:)Take all the time you need.
So are we gonna talk about last night?
(Penny:)-Are you ready to apologize?
-No.
Ehh! Wrong answer.
But thank you for playing.
(Leonard:)Come on. This is stupid.
(Penny:)Oh, there it is again.
You think I'm stupid.
(Leonard:)No. There's a difference
between being and acting stupid.
(Penny:)Oh, yeah? Well, there's a difference
between being a jerk and being an ass.
No, there isn't. They're synonyms.
(Raj:)Well, that was rather unpleasant.
(Howard:)Yeah. I don't think I need
my pre-show urination anymore.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, when that woman moved in
three years ago...
(Sheldon:)...I told you not to talk to her.
Now look, we are late for the movies.